（生徒たちの話し声）
（生徒たちの笑い声）
（クク）タラオ！ トマト食べる？
Tarao! Want a tomato?
（タラオ）ありがとう
（クク）フフッ
Thank you.
Bên này nè.
（生徒１）こっちだよ　ハハハ！
（生徒２）待って！
Chờ với.
（生徒１）おいで ほらー！
Ô kê.
（トキオ）ミミヒメ？
Mimihime.
何をボヤーっとしてるの？
授業 始まるよ
What are you daydreaming for?
Class is about to start.
（ミミヒメ）うん
We have a test today.
今日はテストがあるよ
えっ！ 今日は普通に授業だろ？
What? Today's just a normal class, right?
But, we do have one.
でも あるよ
Get ready for the test.
（教師ロボット）
テストをします
-Huh?
-You never said.
（トキオ）えっ！ 聞いてないよ
（タカ）はあ？
先生 勉強してないからムリです
Teacher! I haven't studied at all.
It's impossible.
Even if you had, it'd be impossible.
（アンズ）
君は勉強しても無理だけどねえ
What?
（タカ）ああ？
（アンズ）フフン
（手を叩く音）
Everyone, please be quiet.
（教師ロボット）ハイ 静かに
普段の授業を受けていればできます
If you paid attention in class,
you'll be fine.
（電子音）
There are ten questions.
全10問です
（タカ）ん～…
（絵を描く音）
Why does the fish have arms?
なんでこの魚 手が生えてるの？
Well, to catch other fish of course.
（コナ）さあ 他の魚を
捕まえるためかな？
（クク）こんなの見たの？
Have you seen one before?
いーや 想像だよ
No, I just made it up!
（クク）ふーん
Okay.
ヘンだねえ
It's weird.
Strange, right?
ヘンかな
（クク）でも 面白い絵だから
園長先生に見せてあげようよ
Yeah, but I want to show the Director.
It's funny!
そんで 僕にちょうだい
Can I have it?
-When I've finished it, okay?
-Okay.
（コナ）描き終わったらね
（クク）うん
（教師ロボット）残り15分です
Fifteen minutes left.
Geez! Come on.
げえっ おいおい…
（ノイズ音）
ん？
（トキオ）外の…
Outside of…
外？
the outside?
（石を蹴る音）
（足音）
（マル）ねえ 宝探ししようか
So, shall we go hunting for treasure?
Sure, okay.
（キルコ）うーん そうだねえ…
This neighborhood
doesn't seem too messed up.
この辺は破壊が少ないし
We need to find houses
that haven't been broken into.
荒らされてなさそうな家
見つけたらねえ
じゃあ もっと奥行こうよ
Let's go further in then.
It's locked. That's a good sign.
（キルコ）鍵かかってる… 有望！
あら？ マル どこ行ったー？
マルーっ！
Wait, Maru? Where are you? Hey, Maru!
Sis! We can get in from over here!
（マル）おねーちゃーん！
ここから入れそう
これだけガラスが
残ってるってことは
The windows are barely broken.
I guess no one's been in here yet.
やっぱ荒らされてないね
結構 傷んでるねえ
Oh, it's a total wreck.
僕 奥の方見てくる
I'll go and check the other rooms.
ん…んっ
Oh, got a toothbrush.
（キルコ）おっ 歯ブラシ ゲット
（マル）おねーちゃん！
Sis!
I found an unopened pack of toilet paper!
開けてないトイレットペーパー
Nice one. I'm dying!
ナイスナイス！ 僕 トイレしたい
Oh, no!
あらら…
よっと…
ああ～
Having a toilet makes all the difference,
even if it doesn't work.
形だけでも便器があると
気分が違うね～
（足音）
ってオイ！ 見んなよ！
Hey, don't look!
Well, shut the door then.
ドア閉めないから…
あれば閉めるさ！
There is no door.
はあ…
（木がきしむ音）
As if, the roof is wide open.
（キルコ）
ありゃ 屋根に穴開いてるじゃん
That's why this place is a dump.
こりゃ 傷むわけだ
I'm so hungry.
（マル）お腹すいたー
Don't say it.
（キルコ）やめろよ も～
（ドアが開く音）
なるべく考えないようにしてたのに
I'm trying not to think about it.
あっ…
What is it--
どうかし… あっ
あ…
（足音）
災害の後 生き残れなかった人の
ほとんどは餓死だって話だ
Most of the people who survived
ended up dying of starvation.
家の中で死んでるってことは…
Since they died in this house,
ここに食べ物なんて残ってない
it means there's no food here.
次… 行こうか
Let's go to the next house.
（マル）うん…
Okay.
Sis, this house is amazing.
（マル）
お姉ちゃん この家すごいよ
It's so glamorous.
なんか全体的に豪華
Yeah, the people who lived here
must have been super rich.
（キルコ）うん 金持ちでも
住んでたんだなー
Wow, you finally opened the canned food?
あっ！　ついに開けるの？
缶詰！
食べるもん
なんも見つかんなかったかんねー
Well, we didn't exactly
find anything to eat, did we?
マル君 なんかお皿探してきて
Maru, can you find us
some plates or something?
On it. I'm starved.
よっしゃあ！ 腹がなるぜ
（マル）
ねえ この野菜っぽいの何？
Hey, what's this veg stuff?
そこらへんに生えてた草の
食べられそうなやつ
The weeds growing all over the place
around here. I think they're edible.
少しでも腹の足しになるかと思って
I thought it might fill us up a bit more.
へえ～　あーん…
んっ…！
（マル）うーわ 青くっさ にっが！
（キルコ）まっず！ 出して出して
-It's so bitter.
-Spit it out!
（せき込み）
It stunk out the whole dish.
もう～ なんか全体的に臭いが
移っちゃってるよ～
I'm sorry!
う… ごめーん
貴重な缶詰だったんだろー！
That was our precious canned food!
I said I'm sorry!
（キルコ）ごめんて～
（マル）
それ お姉ちゃんの恋人？
Is that your boyfriend?
起きてたのかっ
You're awake?
（マル）俺 寝付きが悪いんだよ
I can never fall asleep.
いつもお姉ちゃんのほうが
先に寝るよ
You're always fast asleep way before me.
Really?
I guess I'm a useless bodyguard then.
あ… そうだったのか
ボディガード失格だ
別に俺１人でも大丈夫だから
I'm fine protecting myself.
You can go back if you want.
帰ってもいいよ
One is my friend, and the other
is someone I want to see.
これは親友と
ちょっと会いたい人なんだけど
If I can find them
while I take you to your destination,
君を目的地まで
連れてくついでに探せたら
一石二鳥だと思ってんの
that'll be two birds with one stone.
だから君といるのは有意義だよ
That's why it's important
I tag along with you.
（マル）んん…
ま 僕は寝てる間に
どっか行ったりしないから
Anyway, I'm not gonna go anywhere
while you're sleeping,
安心して寝ろ
so you can relax.
（雷の音）
（風の吹き荒れる音）
（鳴き声）
So, where shall we go today?
（キルコ）
さて… 今日はどっち行こうか
We don't have enough info to go on.
（マル）もう いい加減
情報が足りないよね
俺ら当てもなく さまよいすぎ
I'm sick of wandering around aimlessly.
（キルコ）
ハハハ… じゃ 人探そう 人
Well then, let's start looking for others.
Let's go somewhere that might be busy.
人のいそうな方に行こう
（マル）人がまとまって
住んでるとすりゃあ
A place where people gather,
土のある所か 駅の近く… かな
like somewhere with land,
or near a station.
（キルコ）そんなトコだろうねえ
Yeah, somewhere like that.
とりあえず こう
線路に沿って歩こう
For now,
let's walk alongside this railway track.
そうだ！ 俺 新しい靴欲しい
Great! And I want a new pair of shoes.
はいはい 道々探そうね
Okay, okay.
Let's keep an eye out for a store.
And after that,
I'm desperate for some tasty food!
あと なんかおいしいもの食べたい
Are you still annoyed at me
for yesterday, or what?
君ね まだ昨日のこと
根に持ってんの？
え？
That's not what I meant!
あっー いや！
そんなつもりで
言ったんじゃなくて…
君という男は——
Guys like you
are always saying stupid stuff like that,
even if it is by mistake.
悪気があってのことでもない
人の失敗を そうやって…
あ…
Women!
（盗賊１）女だ！
（盗賊２）うっしゃあ！
生きてたかいがあった
Just when I thought life
wasn't worth living.
（盗賊３）女 ２人だ
Two women appear.
俺は男だ
I'm a man.
チッ… なんだ オスのガキか
Great, a little brat boy.
I'm a boy too.
僕も男だぞ
I'm not stupid!
ウソつけ！
All right, put down your heavy bags.
よーし 荷物置いて
おとなしく座れ
I'm gonna take you to heaven.
天国に連れてってやるからよ
（キルコ）はあ…
Just when I thought we'd found someone
せっかく人に会ったかと思えば
ロクなのがいない…
it's just a couple of bums.
おおっ！
Whoa, wait. We don't have many bullets.
Don't waste them.
（マル）
やめときなよ　弾がもったいない
Get outta here if you want to live!
お前ら 死にたくなかったら
どっか行け！
俺たちの命は弾以下だってよ
So our lives are worth less than bullets.
こいつら 物心ついた時には
They're from the lawless generation, whose
world ended before it had even begun.
世界が終わってた
“無法世代〟ってやつだろ
Who knows what they're capable of.
Let's go.
マジで何するか分からねえ
行こうぜ
Not like you could hit us anyway, fools!
どうせ当たんねーと思うけどな
バーカ！
Damn.
（盗賊４）チッ
（盗賊１）ん～ん…
ちょっと待て！ あれ本当に銃か？
Wait a sec. Is that even a real gun?
（盗賊２･３）ん…？
（キルコ）ん…
What's this, what's this?
Dropping it now, are we?
あらあら？ 急に引っ込めたぞ～
I've never seen a gun that weird before.
見たことねえ
ヘンテコな銃だと思ったわ！
You're just bluffing
with some kid's plaything.
オモチャか何かで
ハッタリかましてんな？
フッ…
Run!
逃げるぞ
（盗賊５）逃がすか！
うっ バカにしやがってえ～！
There's no escape!
I won't let you make us look like idiots!
おっと…
うっ…
クッ…
It shoots…
（盗賊４）なんか… 出た
（盗賊たち）うわっ～！
（うめき声）
（キルコ）よう
So, you were saying something
about taking me to heaven?
天国に連れてってくれるとか
言ってたよな？
That was, I--
あれは… その…
ひいっ ひ…
We're looking for it. Heaven.
探してたんだ 天国
案内してよ
Take us there.
（キルコ）へえ…
ごたいそうな所に住んでるねえ
Wow, what a flashy home you guys have.
どう？ マル
何かピンとくることは？
What do you think, Maru?
Anything catch your attention?
うん… なんにもない
No, nothing.
（キルコ）だろうねえ
Right?
There's no way this is the goal.
It'd be a miracle.
ここがゴールだったら奇跡だよ
Oh, there's a generator!
That's a generator, right?
あっ 発電機だ！ 発電機だよね？
この電池 充電できない？
Can you charge my battery?
Why would I do that?
なんでそんなことをしな… うっ…
I don't think you're really grasping
the full reality of your situation.
まだ立場が分かってねえようだな
オッサン
You attacked us,
but we turned the tables on you.
あんたら人のこと襲っといて
返り討ちにあったんだよ？
ひいっ… う…
命取られても文句言えないんだよ
Even if I decide to kill you,
you don't have the right to complain.
We'll leave once the battery is full.
この電池満タンにしてくれたら
出てってやるから…
Please.
頼むよ
（盗賊２）ううっ…
はあ…
And while we're at it, you guys
heard of a place called "Heaven"?
あとダメ元で一応聞くけど
天国って場所に心当たりないかな？
この際ナントカ天国って名前でも
At this point, anywhere
with "heaven" in its name,
or even a place you think
feels "just like heaven" will do.
まるで天国って感じでも
いいんだけど
崩壊以来 天国みたいな場所なんて
あの世にしかねーよ
As if anything like heaven exists
since the Collapse.
I understand that.
んなこと分かってんだよ…
That's why I tried to
make the question simpler for you.
だからハードル下げてんじゃん
（盗賊４）
あんたら トマト好きか？
Do you guys like tomatoes?
（盗賊２）ん？
They're back.
おっ 帰ってきた
なんで？ くれるの？
Why? Gonna give us some?
If you do, then I've heard of something
you might call "heaven."
トマト好きにとっちゃあ
天国と言えなくもない話なら
聞いたことがある
マル君 トマト好き？
-Maru, don't you like tomatoes?
-Love them.
好き
Tell us the details.
詳しく聞かせて
Here.
（盗賊２）ほれ
Oh, thank you so much!
おっ ありがとー！
なんの電池なんだ？ それ
What kind of battery is that exactly?
My gun battery.
この銃の
You little brat!
（盗賊たち）てっ てめえ！
You've been controlling us with a gun
that doesn't work this whole time.
（盗賊２）じゃ… じゃあずっと
撃てない銃で制圧してたのか！
I wasn't even sure that last shot
was gonna fire. I was out of bullets.
最後の一発も
出るか怪しかったんだよ
弾切れで
くう… くくっ
（キルコ）ね マル
Right, Maru?
Morons! I hope you die by the roadside.
Lawless youths!
（盗賊３）バカヤロー！
野垂れ死ね　無法世代のガキ！
You should respect your elders!
（盗賊５）大人ナメるな！
（盗賊たち）うわあっ！
ハッ　アハハ　アハハハッ！
Phew, that was close.
（マル）あー 怖かったあ
It was no big deal.
Just a bunch of old idiots.
（キルコ）どってことないでしょ
あんなオッサンたち
We got this charged up too!
これ充電できたし
I feel so much better
now we've got four shots.
あと４発撃てると思うと心強い
４発目は計算に入れないほうがいい
It's probably better not to
count it as four shots.
The number of times
that thing doesn't work…
出ないことのほうが多いもん
Well anyway, off to "Tomato Heaven."
そんじゃ トマト天国を目指すか
（マル･キルコ）フフフ…
（マル）トマト天国て…
What the hell is "Tomato Heaven"?
（足音）
I'm not really sure
that's the best way to hold an exam.
（アンズ）ああいう
テストのやり方はどうかと思うよ
（アンズ）何か不名誉な
名前を付けるべきだよね
Mimihime, how did you know there
was going to be a test?
（トキオ：小声）ミミヒメは
なんでテストがあるって分かったの
（タカ）
ああ だまし討ちとか
分かんないよ
なんとなく予感がしただけ
I don't know. I just had a hunch somehow.
闇討ちみたいな
名前にすべきだ
（アンズ）それいいね
But there is one thing that is certain.
ただ１つだけ確かなことがある
テストがあると
分かっていたからといって
Just because you know there's a test,
there's no promise of full marks.
問題が解けるとは限らない
（トキオ）ええ…
Class is done! Let's play some sport.
（タカ）まあ 今日の授業は
終わったことだし運動しようぜ！
（シロ）僕 続き作りたいから
I want to continue working on this, so…
（タカ）じゃあ アンズ
Then, Anzu?
お断り
No thanks.
君と競っても
勝てるわけないんだから
There's no way I can win against you.
Tokio?
トキオ…
トキオは僕と話があるの ね？
Tokio has something
to discuss with me. Right?
うあっ
（トキオ）うわ…
（ミミヒメ）えへっ
そんじゃ
コナに相手してもらおうかなっ！
Fine then.
I guess I'll get Kona to play with me.
（生徒）わあっ
はっ…
なんだろうね あの運動神経
Where on earth
does he get reflexes like that?
（タカ）コーナ！
Kona!
（自販機の音）
（ミミヒメ）さっきテスト中に
外がどうとか言ってたよね
You said something about
the outside during the test, didn't you?
No, that was…
（トキオ）あ… いや あれは…
（ミミヒメ）トキオは
外がどうなってると思う？
What do you think
the outside is like, Tokio?
外？
Outside?
うーん… どうと言われても
Why would you ask--
（ミミヒメ）違う この壁の外
Not here. Outside this wall.
Huh? There's an outside beyond the wall?
（トキオ）
えっ？ ここより外があるの？
何もないんじゃないの？
Isn't it just nothing?
I think there is something else.
あると思うよ
僕は ずっとそんな気が
してたんだけどね
I've always had a feeling that there is.
And recently,
I've been able to imagine it more clearly.
最近 だんだんイメージが
ハッキリしてきたの
When I think about wanting to go outside,
僕が外に出たいな
出たいなーって思ってると
外から２人の人が
僕を助けに来てくれるの
two people from the outside come
to help me, and one of their faces…
その１人の顔が
トキオにそっくりなんだ
…is exactly the same as yours.
（足音）
Outside the room…
（トキオ）部屋の外…
outside the school…
学校の外…
外の…
outside of…
外？
the outside.
（園長先生）トキオ君
（足音）
Tokio?
（トキオ）園長先生
Director.
If you can't sleep,
do you want some medicine?
（猿渡さわたり）
眠れないなら お薬を出そうか？
No, I…
（トキオ）いえ… あの…
ここより外って あるんですか？
Is there an outside beyond this one?
ん…？
それは トキオ君が考えたの？
Did you think of that yourself?
Mimihime did.
（トキオ）ミミヒメが…
あの子は勘の鋭いところが
ありますからね
That girl has a sharp intuition.
Director.
（青島あおしま）園長…
It's only a matter of time
before they find out. Don't worry.
（園長）いずれ知ってもらう
ことです　構いません
トキオ君
Tokio?
あ…
There is an outside beyond here.
（園長）
ここより外はあります
Hey, Maru,
（キルコ）ねえ マル
it may surprise you to hear this,
coming from your bodyguard--
ボディガードの僕が
こんなこと言ったら
びっくりしちゃうだろうけど…
I'm pretty sure nothing you say
could surprise me anymore.
（マル）もうお姉ちゃんの
言うことに いちいち驚かないよ
I can't walk any further.
もう歩けない
What?
えーっ！
What? We've been sleeping outdoors,
traversing mountains.
（キルコ）だって野宿したり
山超えたり 限界だよ！
（荷物を置く音）
I've reached my limit.
There's nothing to eat, nowhere to sleep.
I can't go on.
こんなに資源も寝るとこも
ない場所が続くなんて
All that talk of there being shops
on every corner before the Collapse…
崩壊前は日本中徒歩５分圏内に
なんでも売ってる店があったって…
Was it all a lie?
あれはウソなのかー！
It's just because
we are on a path between cities.
（マル）
街と街の間は こんなもんだよ
都会で育ったんだねえ～
You're a city girl, aren't you?
Exactly.
I'm a Tokyo girl through and through.
あーそうさ　こちとら江戸っ子よ
Ouch.
イッテ… あ…
せめて寝れそうな所 探そう
Let's at least find
a decent spot to sleep.
Where do you get so much energy from?
Is it because you're young?
なんでそんな体力あんの？
若いから？
We're basically the same age.
たいして年 変わんないでしょ
（キルコ）マル君 15歳だっけ？
You're 15, right?
（マル）たぶん… お姉ちゃんは？
I think so. You?
（キルコ）僕は18… いや 20かな
I'm 18, wait, 20.
What's with the two-year gap?
（マル）なんで２年も開きがあるの
（キルコ）算数 苦手なんだよ
I'm not good with numbers, okay?
No way.
（キルコ）ウソだろ…
（マル･キルコ）ああっ…
（キルコ）営業してんの コレ？
That place is open?
We are, yes.
（女将おかみ）やってるよ
（キルコ）あっ…
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
（女将）９ 10 11 12！
はーい 確かに
All right, that'll do.
Are you sure it's enough? It's so cheap.
本当にそれでいいの？
安すぎない？
なんか悪いから これどうぞ
I feel bad. Take these too.
（カバンを開ける音）
（女将）え？ いいの？
Wow, AA batteries! Thank you!
単三電池！ ありがたーい
Can I look at the guest book?
この宿帳 見てもいいですか？
Go for it.
いいよ～
You can't get batteries like this anymore!
こんな状態のいい電池がねえ～
And in a place like this!
あるところには あるんだねー
いないか…
He's not in here.
Have you ever seen these two here?
こういう人 来たことないですかね
He's good-looking. If I had, I'd remember.
（女将）
あらイイ男　来たら忘れんね
What are their names?
名前は？
Robin Inazaki.
（キルコ）稲崎いなざき露敏ろびん
Well, I really don't know.
うーん 分からんなあ…
What about the older, punky-looking one?
もう１人のパンクなおじさんは？
I don't know his name.
名前は… 分かんない
みんな 医者とか先生って
呼んでたからな…
Everyone called him "Doc" or "Sir."
I see.
（女将）それじゃあねえ…
Oh, before I forget, have you ever heard
of a place called "Heaven"?
あっ あと 天国って場所で
何か思い当たることないですか？
んーん…
Well, that's how
everyone describes this place.
ま みんなここで言うけどね
It's heaven!
天国だ～！
（引き戸が開く音）
Kiruko.
（女将）キルコちゃん
（キルコ）ひいっ！ うっ…
（キルコ）うっ… いあっ… はいっ
Y-yes.
うっ あのっ… ああ… 鏡！
The mirror.
いやー 鏡が割れてるな～
なんて見てたんですよ！
That's a huge crack in the mirror!
I was just looking at it.
はあ…
The shower doesn't work,
but you can use the hot bath water.
シャワー出ないから
湯船のお湯 桶おけで使ってね
There are plenty of bottles,
but just use what you need.
それから ボトルたくさんあるけど
適当に使って
The one that foams nicely is the shampoo.
ア… ハハ…
いい感じに泡が出るやつが
シャンプーね
（キルコ）ええ…！
蓄電ほとんどできないから
日のあるうちに使ってね
We don't have power reserves here,
you need to use that while the sun is up.
はーい
Got it.
（ドライヤーの音）
Excuse me,
（キルコ）女将さん
あのケースって
もしかして銃ですか？
that case, is it a gun case?
Uh-huh. There's a monster
that prowls around this area.
ああ… このへんには
怪物が出るからね
Don't go out wandering at night.
夜は出歩いちゃだめだよ
（ドライヤーを切る音）
-Monster…
-Hiruko.
怪物って…
（マル）ヒルコ！
（キルコ）人食いのことですか？
You mean a "Man-eater"?
はっ…
People call it different things,
人によって呼び方は
まちまちなんですが
こう… 大きくて
ぐちゃぐちゃっとした形で
but it's this big, confusing shape,
and it eats people.
人を食べるやつ！
We can kill it.
僕ら それ殺せますよ
That's-- Guns have no effect on it.
（女将）
あんな… 銃も効かないのに…
We'll do it.
（キルコ）やれますよ！
My Kiru-Beam works on it, and this kid--
キル光線なら効きますし この子の
うっ… キル光線？
Kiru-Beams?
What?
（キルコ）何さ
（マル）キル光線…
Kiru-Beam…
キルコの光線だからキル光線…
Just because it's your beam,
you named it after yourself?
Why do you need the details?
（キルコ）なんべんもなんべんも
確認すんな！
You already think it's weird anyway.
変なこと言ったかと思うだろ！
（吹きこぼれる音）
Exactly, it's weird.
That's why I'm asking.
（マル）変だから確認したんだよ
（女将）イノシシか何かの肉と
野菜の煮たものでよかったら
I've made a stew with some kind of
boar meat and vegetables, if you like?
Really, we can have some?
え？ い… いいんですか？ ごはん
おいしい！
It's really good!
I wanted to discuss
something with you both.
あなたたちを食事に誘ったのは
Well, it's a bit tricky to find the words.
言いにくいことなんだけど…
（キルコ）んっ…
（マル）あ…
Even though you two were raised
in these strange times,
こんな状況の中で育ったのに
今もきちんとお箸が使えてて
ちゃんと教育を受けている
子たちだと思うから…
you use chopsticks perfectly,
and seem to have been educated well.
おせっかいかも知れないけれど
言わせてもらうわね
I may be meddling,
but I have to say something.
It's not my opinion,
or a rule or anything,
近親者同士で
子供を作るというのは…
決まりとか
気持ちの問題じゃなくて
but having children with a close relative,
遺伝子的な 根本的なところに
危険があるの！
genetically speaking,
is fundamentally dangerous!
What are you trying to say?
なんの話をしてますか…？
（マル）うあっ
He might keep calling me "Sis,"
この子がお姉ちゃんって呼ぶから
勘違いさせたかもしれませんけど
う… ここ 血つながってないんで！
but we are not even slightly related!
それにそもそも
そういう関係ではございませーん！
And more to the point,
we are not even dating!
え？
I got completely the wrong idea!
やだ おばちゃん早とちり！
勘弁してくださいよ！
Give me a break!
ん～… 僕は東京で
なんでも屋というか
I do all kinds of stuff in Tokyo,
I'm sorta like an odd-job girl.
便利屋みたいなことをやってて
I received a request to be
this guy's bodyguard during his travels.
この子の旅のボディーガード
依頼を受けたんです
警護対象以上の感情は
ありませんから～
He is nothing to me
beyond an object of my protection.
（キルコ）どしたの マル？
なんか急に元気ないね
What's wrong, Maru?
Why are you suddenly so down?
Why are you dragging your futon
so far away?
なんでそんな布団 離すの？
Hey, are you mad about something?
ねえ なんか怒ってんの？
（マルの吐く息）
（寝息）
Geez.
（マル）なんだよ
So today you fall asleep straightaway…
今日は えらく寝付きいいじゃん
May as well go to sleep too then.
さてと 僕も寝るかなあ…
おっとっ あっ…
あれ…
Wow.
疲れてるせいかな…
Am I really that tired?
なんか…
Something…
ヘン… だ
feels strange…
（銃を取り出す音）
Is there an outside beyond this one?
（トキオ）
ここより外って あるんですか？
There is an outside beyond here.
ここより外は あります
However, it is a filthy world, a hell…
ただし 浅ましい怪物が
うごめく汚れた世界
where abhorrent monsters lurk.
地獄です
♪～
もういいかい
もういいよ
見えてるものだけじゃほら
理解できない心を
もういいかい
もう一回
選べない未来ならば僕らが選ぶはなんだ？
感情も
妄想も
もはや意味をなさないな
崩れた街がにやつく
確かなものなんてない
わかるはずがないのに
それでも確かめたいのだから
見せたくないものばかりを
見せないから
大事なものさえも見つからない
綺麗なままでいることはできないじゃない
僕らは
進もう
～♪